What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... Day of Farewells
Kobato!
Why are you laughing in your sleep?
Was I laughing?
You seemed incredibly happy.
Must've been a great dream.
Yeah!
A long time ago, I-
Huh?
Um...
It was a very, very happy dream.
It was about the place you want to go, right?
Closing Notice
We regret to announce
the closing of this
nursery.
Any further questions
should be directed
to the headmistress,
Okiura Sayaka.
Yomogi Nursery
Okiura Sayaka
Good morning!
Good morning, Kobato.
Where are we cleaning up today?
I'm leaving.
Sure, go ahead.
It's such a pant having to deal with all of these.
Don't worry! I'll try my best!
That's right. We've got to move on.
Move on, huh.
Once you've got it all tied up, can you put it in the hall?
Sure.
After this, why don't we take a break?
Okay.
It's kind of tough without Fujimoto around.
He must be busy at work.
Thank you.
You shouldn't overwork yourself.
No, I want to keep going.
You don't need to work so much.
If you want to fire me, why don't you say that.
That's not it!
I don't get you...
Sorry.
For deciding to close the nursery.
There's only thing I'd like you to understand.
I've come to terms with it.
I have no regrets.
It's not because Okiura told me to.
In the end, I made the decision.
That's how I feel.
Okay..
What?
Would you mind coming to the nursery?
There's still a few things of yours.
No.
Throw it all out.
But...
I'm busy. I can't go.
This is Fujimoto.
Sorry, I'll be about an hour late.
Fujimoto?
Look out!
Huh?
I thought you said you were going to be late.
I got done early.
Why do you look so worried?
You're gonna ruin my mood, too.
Sorry...
What are you worrying about?
What do you want to do?
I don't know...
But...
But?
It hurts here.
Miss Sayaka said she was fine with Yomogi Nursery closing down, but...
Even still...
Is this about Fujimoto?
What about him?
What do you mean, what about him?
Don't you realize you're-
Oh man. Figures.
Kiyokazu?
Good morning.
You have work today?
Yeah.
But today's the day they're tearing down the-
I'm leaving now.
He could have at least taken the day off...
All right.
If he's gone, I'm leaving too.
Are you going out?
Yeah. I'll be back later tonight.
Don't make that face!
Okay...
Come on.
You need to hurry up, or you'll be late.
Okay.
Looks good.
You have everything out of there, ma'am?
We were able to move everything yesterday.
All right, let's get started.
Where's that guy that's always glaring at people?
He had to work.
Man, no grace at all.
He spent so much time here, too. That's cold.
I don't think it's cold!
Fujimoto's busy!
Sorry.
Anyway, Okiura told me to take care of you today.
Because he won't be around for a while.
Yes, I heard.
Seems like he's having trouble higher up.
Goons like me don't really get to know about that stuff.
Then Okiura's-
Don't worry.
He'll be fine.
After all, he's Okiura.
Miss Sayaka!
Kobato!
Everybody!
What are you doing here?
Today is goodbye.
So we came to see you.
I asked mom!
Right. Thanks.
Hey, boss, can we get started?
Can we start, ma'am?
Please do.
It's dangerous. Let's stand back.
Okay.
Yeah, go for it!
Bye-bye...
I'll tell you one more time.
There's no point talking with him.
Give it up.
You're so mean, Genko!
Going on break before me. Mmmmm.
Zuisho!
Quiet down.
What!? You're going to try and catch a Bunny!?
Yeah. With a Bunny hostage, he'll have to talk.
Do you really think God will fall for that?
It's better than doing nothing.
With how we are now, it's not that simple.
Ginsei's right.
He's being a lot more straightforward than you, too.
Simple or no, we can fix that later.
Knock it off.
Didn't you learn anything last time?
Please, you two!
Are you trying to catch his attention?
You know who's gonna take the brunt of it, right? If you don't, I'll be glad to show you.
Sorry.
Fine.
Maybe what God was trying to teach you...
Is how to wait.
Well, I sure am bad at it.
Hey!
Fine, fine. I won't do anything.
I am Iorogi. I will accompany you.
Once we're done, the lot will be off limits, ma'am.
Understood. Thank you.
Take care, okay?
Later.
It seemed so big from inside...
But looking at it like this...
Right?
Kobato, can you do me a favor?
Yeah.
I want you to be there for Fujimoto.
I think Yomogi was holding him back.
Holding him back? How?
It's why he's always working so hard.
I relied on him too much, too.
I wish I had realized sooner.
Thanks, Fujimoto.
Mister Kiyokazu!
Play the organ!
You should tell him to do what he likes for his own sake.
But he's really enthusiastic!
Yeah. That's exactly why you need to.
Because he always tries too hard.
So please take care of him, Kobato.
Stay by his side.
What about you?
That's not my place.
Not anymore.
Kobato!
I'm home!
Terrible news, Kobato!
Domoto... You...
Just like I promised, I didn't contact anyone from Yomogi.
I only talked to Chitose.
Sorry, Kobato. He said he didn't want to make you worry.
Isn't it like him to be worried about that?
Um... Your arm...
I'm glad you weren't hurt too badly.
Try not to overdo it, okay? Everyone's worried about you.
It must be inconvenient only being able to use one hand. If there's anything I can do, just ask.
I told you when we first met.
If you're just doing this out of pity or self-sacrifice, stay away.
If you're just going to feel sorry for me, don't.
It's not like that!
You're annoying!
It's not like that, Fujimoto...
It's not like that...
For me?
He's telling you you have until the next full moon to gather candy.
If you don't, you know what the agreement is.
Hey, Bunny!
How can I extend that deadline?
What's going to happen now?
What do you think we should do?
Dunno. It's all up to him.
He really seems like he feels guilty.
If not for that fight, she would have...
If he had taken that blow, it wouldn't have happened.
If there's anything I can do, I'll do it!
Just give her four more seasons!
No, just one more!
Look!
Isn't there anything!?
Wait!
In between the things I've lost
and the things I've been able to hold on to,
Your smile falls in that gap
It seems like I can reach it, but I can't
I can't fly
I just wanted to make you smile
My two wings weren't good enough
Why do I even have them?
Just smiling by your side
is all I can do.
Just warming you is good enough,
even though I want to embrace you
Even with these scarred, worthless wings,
right now I can smile
Next episode: "... Kobato's Wish"